mrgoodlife.net 2014-11-21

# PRIVACY POLICY | MR.GOODLIFE. - The Online Magazine for the Goodlife.

### PRIVACY POLICY

The following Privacy Policy covers all the websites (“websites”) owned, affiliated or operated by MR.GOODLIFE LLC (“MR.GOODLIFE LLC ”, “we”, “us”, “our”). It is our goal to bring you information tailored to your personal interests but, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**By visiting MR.GOODLIFE LLC’s websites, submitting information or using any of our products and services, you are accepting the practiced outlined in this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information that MR.GOODLIFE LLC gathers when you are on our websites and when you are using MR.GOODLIFE LLC services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers MR.GOODLIFE LLC ’s treatment of any personal information that MR.GOODLIFE LLC’s business partners share with us. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to and from the website as well as the practices of third parties that MR.GOODLIFE LLC does not control or own, or individuals thatMR.GOODLIFE LLC does not employ or manage.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of our websites constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time so check back often. Continued access of our websites by you will constitute your acceptance of the changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**1\. Introduction**

Thank you for visiting MR.GOODLIFE. This Privacy Policy is written to better explain how we collect and use your information. This Privacy Policy is a binding contract and you must agree to it to the same extent as our Terms and Conditions in order to use our services.

**2\. Information You Provide to Us**

The website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. This includes but is not limited to when you register for our community, enter a sweepstakes and complete a survey. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features such as posting on our community.

**3\. Automatic Information**

Our servers may automatically collect information about your computer when you visit our websites, including without limitation the website that referred you, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) and other usage and traffic information. MR.GOODLIFE LLC uses this statistical information to analyze trends, gather demographic information and administer our websites so we may provide improved web experiences to our readers. The information is not in a manner that would identify you personally. We may provide statistical information, not personal information, to our partners about how our users, collectively use our websites. We share this information to our partners, so that they may further understand the usage of their areas and our websites, so that they too could provide you with a better web experience. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

**4\. Use of Information**

We may use your information:

To enhance or improve user experience, the website, or service.  
To send e-mails about the site or respond to inquiries.  
To send e-mails about the website and other products, news, or updates for mrgoodlife.net  
To send e-mails about third parties’ products or services.

**5\. Cookies**

In order to distinguish you from other users—especially other users on the same network as you — we need to use cookies to track your specific computer. Specifically, we use cookies to save your preferences, keep track of advertisements, and remember your shopping cart items. Additionally, our cookies may be accessible by third parties, or provided by third parties. For example, we use Google AdSense on our website, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to better target ads that you may find interesting or relevant. For these reasons we require that you keep cookies enabled when using our website.

**6\. Third Party Websites**

We may link to third party websites from our own website. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party websites or their use of your personal information. We recommend that you review their privacy policies and other agreements governing your use of their website.

**7\. Third Party Access to Your Information**

We protect your information from being accessed by third parties. However, since we may employ outside maintenance personnel or use a third party to host our material, there are third party entities which may have custody or access to your information. Because of this, it is necessary that you permit us to give access to your information to third parties to the same extent that you authorize us to do so. For greater certainty, every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. Additionally, we may store your information or share it with certain other third parties for reason that may or may not be related to maintenance, advertising, marketing, or other purposes related to our business. The following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share, or transfer your information with:

– Google Analytics

**8\. Law Enforcement**

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.

**9\. Security of Information**

We use SSL certificates to help secure our website. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**10\. Amendments**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our website in place of the old version. We will also include the date that the currently displayed Privacy Policy took effect to help you determine whether there have been any changes since you last used our website. Like our Terms of Service, you must visit this page each time you come to our website and read and agree to it if the date it was last modified is more recent than the last time you agreed to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

**11\. Contact**

Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, can be directed to info@mrgoodlife.net
